happy roasts everyone happy rose what a
crowd Here I am again following
DeNiro great job ageing ball
I learned something tonight alec is the
name you give your son if you want them
to grow up and be an kaylynn you
were awesome tonight
I just want to say that you were really
awesome tonight
but I wouldn't you with Bruce
Jenner's dick
[Applause]
remember when your picture was on
Wheaties boxes back when people could
still look at you when they eat
[Applause]
how about a hand for a guest of honor
mr. Alec bobblehead Baldwin Alec is
actually my neighbor in Greenwich
Village which was a pretty safe
neighborhood until you moved in
you're a big star I watched you get
arrested for punching a guy over a
parking spot
next time valet your car and help your
brother's business help a brother round
Alec I'm speaking as a big fan I love
all your movies Alec I loved you in The
Departed which is also what Caitlin
calls her penis and of course Alec you
got your oscar nomination for the cooler
which is where caitlin keeps her penis
and of course your first big break was
The Hunt for Red October which is what
Caitlin calls her vagina
alik I first saw you in the movie Pearl
Harbor which was worse than the actual
Pearl Harbor halfway through I was
rooting for the Japanese any fans of
Alec Baldwin's Donald Trump impression
here tonight a lot of people don't
realize is that for the last three years
Donald Trump is actually doing an Alec
Baldwin impression because people name
CEOs at the press he married an
immigrant half his age the only
difference is in Trump calls his
daughter a fox not a pig
here's to you Ireland great job Ireland
you didn't wink once what a babe I love
that movie Bob this is nothing for you
you've seen it all
Robert Dino's been around so long he was
God's father
[Applause]
[Music]